Pre-social media, no one ever really knew about folks.
Right.
Well, I don't really try to go into anybody else's business
because you can't really speak on other people's situations.
But, I mean, I worked with Destiny Chow right before their split
with Latavia and Latoya.
So, of course, you know, I kind of was hearing the things that were happening.
So, I mean, you know, I feel like every group has its situation.
And their stuff, right?
Yeah.
Back in the day, you know, TLC with Left Eye, God rest her soul.
Remember, she used to be on TV talking about she challenging her group members
to see who could come out with the best solo album.
Like, they always used to have some type of drama that was very public.
So, it's a lot of that.
It is.
In every group.